array = [
  {
    id: "c1",
    language: "Css",
    question: `67. `,
    answer: `  `,
  },
  {
    id: "c1",
    language: "Css",
    question: `68. `,
    answer: `  `,
  },

  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: `90. `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: `91. `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: `92. `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: `93.  `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "j1",
    language: "JavaScript",
    question: ` `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `1. What is HTML?`,
    answer: `HTML is short for HyperText Markup Language and is the language of the World Wide Web. It is the standard text formatting language used for creating and displaying pages on the Web. HTML documents are made up of two things: the content and the tags that format it for proper display on pages.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `2. What are tags?`,
    answer: `Content is placed in between HTML tags in order to properly format it. It makes use of the less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol is also used as a closing tag. 
    <strong>sample</strong> `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `3. Do all HTML tags come in a pair?`,
    answer: `No, there are single HTML tags that do not need a closing tag. Examples are the <img> tag and <br> tags.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `4. What are some of the common lists that can be used when designing a page?`,
    answer: `What are some of the common lists that can be used when designing a page? `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `5. How do you insert a comment in HTML?`,
    answer: `Comments in HTML begins with “<!–“nd ends with “–>”. For example: <!-- A SAMPLE COMMENT -->`,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `6. Do all character entities display properly on all systems?`,
    answer: `No, there are some character entities that cannot be displayed when the operating system that the browser is running on does not support the characters. When that happens, these characters are displayed as boxes.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `7. What is an image map?`,
    answer: `Image map lets you link to many different web pages using a single image. You can define shapes in images that you want to make part of an image mapping.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `8. What is the advantage of collapsing white space?`,
    answer: `White spaces are a blank sequence of space characters, which is treated as a single space character in HTML. Because the browser collapses multiple spaces into a single space, you can indent lines of text without worrying about multiple spaces. This enables you to organize the HTML code into a much more readable format.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `9. How do you insert a copyright symbol on a browser page?`,
    answer: `To insert the copyright symbol, you need to type &copy; or & #169; in an HTML file `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `10. How do you create links to sections within the same page?`,
    answer: `Links can be created using the <a> tag, with referencing through the use of the number (#) symbol. For example, you can have one line as <a href=”#topmost”>BACK TO TOP</a>, which would result in the words “BACK TO TOP” appearing on the webpage and links to a bookmark named topmost. You then create a separate tag command like <a name=”topmost”> somewhere on the top of the same webpage so that the user will be linked to that spot when he clicked on “BACK TO TOP”.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `11.  What is the use of alternative text in image mapping?`,
    answer: `Using alternative text lets, you put a descriptive text on each hotspot link. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `12. Do older HTML files work on newer browsers?`,
    answer: `Yes, older HTML files are compliant to the HTML standard. Most older files work on the newer browsers, though some features may not work. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `13.  State  bullet types available in HTML `,
    answer: `With ordered lists, you can select to use some different list types including alphabetical and Roman numerals. The type attribute for unordered lists can be set to disc, square, or circle. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `14. What are applets?`,
    answer: `Applets are small programs that can be embedded within web pages to perform some specific functionality, such as computations, animations, and information processing. Applets are written using the Java language.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `15. What if there is no text between the tags or if a text was omitted by mistake? Will it affect the display of the HTML file?`,
    answer: `If there is no text between the tags, then there is nothing to format. Therefore no formatting will appear. Some tags, especially tags without a closing tag like the <img> tag, do not require any text between them.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `16. How do you create a link that will connect to another web page when clicked?`,
    answer: `To create hyperlinks, or links that connect to another web page, use the href tag. The general format for this is: <a href=”site”>text</a>
    Replace “site” with the actual page URL that is supposed to be linked to when the text is clicked. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `17.  Do <th> tags always need to come at the start of a row or column?`,
    answer: `Any <tr> tag can be changed to a <th> tag. This causes the text contained within the <th> tag to be displayed as bold in the browser. Although <th> tags are mainly used for headings, they do not need to be used exclusively for headings.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `18. What is a marquee?`,
    answer: `A marquee allows you to put a scrolling text in a web page. To do this, place whatever text you want to appear scrolling within the <marquee> and </marquee> tags.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `19.How do you create text on a webpage that will allow you to send an email when clicked? `,
    answer: `<A HREF=”mailto:youremailaddress”>text to be clicked</A> `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `20. Are <br> tags the only way to separate sections of text?`,
    answer: `No. The <br> tag is only one way to separate lines of text. Other tags, like the <p> tag and <blockquote> tag, also separate sections of text.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `21. Are there instances where the text will appear outside of the browser?`,
    answer: `By default, the text is wrapped to appear within the browser window. However, if the text is part of a table cell with a defined width, the text could extend beyond the browser window.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `22. How are active links different from normal links?`,
    answer: `The default color for normal and active links is blue. Some browsers recognize an active link when the mouse cursor is placed over that link; others recognize active links when the link has the focus. Those that don’t have a mouse cursor over that link is considered a normal link.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `23. Which browsers support HTML5?`,
    answer: `The latest versions of Google Chrome, Apple Safari, Mozilla Firefox, and Opera all support most of the HTML5 features. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `24. Name two new tags included in the HTML 5`,
    answer: `<Video> and <Audio> are new tags which are included in HTML5 version. They are mainly used as a replacement for Flash, Silverlight, and similar technologies to play multimedia items.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `25. Do you know which are two semantic tags are included in HTML5 version?`,
    answer: `The <article> and <section> tags are two new tags that are included in HTML5. Articles can be composed of multiple sections that can have multiple articles. An article tag represents a full block of content which is a section of a bigger whole. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `26. HTML <figure> Tag?`,
    answer: `The <figure> tag specifies self-contained content, like illustrations, diagrams, photos, code listings, etc.

    While the content of the <figure> element is related to the main flow, its position is independent of the main flow, and if removed it should not affect the flow of the document. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `27. What happens if the number of values in the rows or cols attribute doesn’t add up to 100 percent?`,
    answer: `The browser sizes the frames relative to the total sum of the values. If the cols attribute is set to 100%, 200% the browser displays two vertical frames with the second being twice as big as the first. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `28. What is the use of Canvas element?`,
    answer: `The canvas element helps to build charts, graphs, bypass Photoshop to create 2D images and place them directly into HTML5 code. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `29. What are the new FORM elements which are available in HTML5?`,
    answer: `The new Form elements in HTML5 offers much better functionality than the earlier versions.

    The tags given provided to carry out these functions are:
    
    1) <datalist> – This tag is use to specify a list of options for input controls.
    
    2) <keygen> – This tag represents a key-pair generator field.
    
    3) <output> – It represents the result of any scripting calculation. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `30. Tell me two benefits of HTML5 Web Storage`,
    answer: `It can store up to 10 MB data which is certainly more than what cookies have.
    Web storage data cannot be transferred with the HTTP request. It helps to increase the performance of the application. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `31.  What is the Application Cache in HTML5 and why it is used?`,
    answer: `The Application Cache concept means that a web application is cached. It can be accessible without the need for internet connection.

    Some advantages of Application Cache:
    
    Offline browsing – Web users can also use the application when they are offline.
    Speed – Cached resources load quicker
    Reduce the server load – The web browser will only download updated resources from the server..
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `32. Explain five new input types provided by HTML5 for forms?`,
    answer: `Date: It allows the user to select a date.
    datetime-local: This input type allows the user to select a date and time without time zone.
    datetime: This input type allows the user to select a date and time with time zone.
    month: It enables the user to select a month and year
    email: These input fields used to contain an e-mail address. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `33. What is formatting in HTML?`,
    answer: `The HTML formatting is a process of format the text for a better look and feel. It uses different tags to make text bold, italicized, underlined. More details.
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `34. Which HTML tag is used to display the data in the tabular form?`,
    answer: `<table>	It defines a table.
    <tr>	It defines a row in a table.
    <th>	It defines a header cell in a table.
    <td>	It defines a cell in a table.
    <caption>	It defines the table caption.
    <colgroup>	It specifies a group of one or more columns in a table for formatting.
    <col>	It is used with <colgroup> element to specify column properties for each column.
    <tbody>	It is used to group the body content in a table.
    <thead>	It is used to group the header content in a table.
    <tfooter>	It is used to group the footer content in a table. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `35. What is the difference between HTML elements and tags?`,
    answer: `HTML elements communicate to the browser to render text. When the elements are enclosed by brackets <>, they form HTML tags. Most of the time, tags come in a pair and surround content.

    `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `36. What is semantic HTML?`,
    answer: `Semantic HTML is a coding style. It is the use of HTML markup to reinforce the semantics or meaning of the content. For example: In semantic HTML <b> </b> tag is not used for bold statement as well as <i> </i> tag is used for italic. Instead of these we use <strong></strong> and <em></em> tags. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `37. How to create a nested webpage in HTML?`,
    answer: `The HTML iframe tag is used to display a nested webpage. In other words, it represents a webpage within a webpage. The HTML <iframe> tag defines an inline frame
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `38. How do you keep list elements straight in an HTML file?`,
    answer: `You can keep the list elements straight by using indents. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `39. Does a hyperlink only apply to text?`,
    answer: `No, you can use hyperlinks on text and images both. The HTML anchor tag defines a hyperlink that links one page to another page
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `40. What is the use of a span tag? Give one example.`,
    answer: `The span tag is used for following things:

    For adding color on text
    For adding background on text
    Highlight any color text `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `41. How to make a picture of a background image of a web page?`,
    answer: `To make a picture a background image on a web page, you should put the following tag code after the </head> tag.

    <body background = "image.gif">  
    Here, replace the "image.gif" with the name of your image file which you want to display on your web page. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `42. What is SVG?`,
    answer: `stands for Scalable Vector Graphics which is used to create vector graphics with the support for interactivity and animation.

    SVG is resolution independent as it does not lose its quality when they are resized or zoomed. SVG images and their behaviors are defined in XML text files. So as XML files, you can create and edit an SVG image with the text editor. It is mostly used for vector type diagrams like pie charts, 2-Dimensional graphs in an X, Y coordinate system. *********************
    <svg width="100" height="100">    
 <circle cx="50" cy="50" r="40" stroke="yellow" stroke-width="4" fill="red" />    
</svg>    **************** `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `43. Which type of video formats are supported by HTML5?`,
    answer: `mp4
    WebM
    Ogg `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `44. Is audio tag supported in HTML 5?`,
    answer: `mp3
    WAV
    Ogg ************ <audio controls>    
    <source src="koyal.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">    
  Your browser does not support the html audio tag.    
  </audio>    *********`,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `45. What is the difference between progress and meter tag?`,
    answer: `The progress tag is used to represent the progress of the task only while the meter tag is used to measure data within a given range. More details. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `46. If I do not put <!DOCTYPE html> will HTML 5 work?`,
    answer: `No, the browser will not be able to identify that it is an HTML document and HTML 5 tags do not function properly..
     `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `47. What is the use of the required attribute in HTML5?
    `,
    answer: `It forces a user to fill text on the text field or text area before submitting the form. It is used for form validation.

    Example:
    
    Name: <input type="text" name="name" required>   `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `48. What are Attributes and how do you use them? `,
    answer: `Each tag has additional attributes that change the way the tag behaves or is displayed. For example, a <input> tag has a type attribute, which you can use to specify whether it’s a text field, checkbox, radio button or one of many more options.
    Attributes are specified directly after the name of the tag, inside the two angled brackets. They should only ever appear in opening tags or in self-closing tags. But, they can never be in closing tags. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `49. Explain the layout of HTML.`,
    answer: `HTML layout specifies a way in which the web page is arranged. Every website has a specific layout to display content in a specific manner. ********** <header>: It is used to define a header for a document or a section.
    <nav>: This defines a container for navigation links
    <section>: It is used to define a section in a document
    <article>: This is used to define an independent, self-contained article
    <aside>: It is used to define content aside from the content
    <footer>: It is used to define a footer for a document or a section `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `50. What is the difference between DIV and SPAN in HTML?`,
    answer: `The difference between span and div is that a span element is in-line and usually used for a small chunk of HTML inside a line,such as inside a paragraph. Whereas, a div or division element is block-line which is equivalent to having a line-break before and after it and used to group larger chunks of code. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `51. Is the <!DOCTYPE html> tag considered as a HTML tag?`,
    answer: `No, the <!DOCTYPE html> declaration is not an HTML tag.

    There are many type of HTML, such as, HTML 4.01 Strict, HTML 4.01 Transitional, HTML 4.01 Frameset, XHTML 1.0 Strict, XHTML 1.0 Transitional, XHTML 1.0 Frameset, XHTML 1.1 etc. So, <!DOCTYPE html> is used to instruct the web browser about the HTML page `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `52. Can you create a multi-colored text on a web page?`,
    answer: `Yes, we can create a multi-colored text on a web page.  To create a multicolor text, you can use <font color =”color”> </font> for the specific texts that you want to color. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `53. What are inline elements and block-level elements in HTML?`,
    answer: `Answer: Block elements are the blocks that take the full available width and always start from a new line. It will stretch itself to the full available width of the available container width. Block-level elements are <div>, <p>, <img>, <section> and many more.

    Inline elements are the elements that will only take the width that is required to fit into the container.
    
    For Example, take the flow of text on the page. When the line of the text takes the full width of the container it wraps itself into a new line and again goes in the same way.
    
    Whereas, the inline element will take only that much space or width that it is needed for them. Inline elements are <span>, <label>, <a>, <b> and many more. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `54. Why Meta tags are used in HTML?`,
    answer: `Meta tags in HTML are used by the developer to tell the browser about the page description, author of the template, character set, keywords and many more.

    Meta tags are used for search engine optimization to tell the search engine about the page contents. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `55. Differentiate between HTML and XHTML.`,
    answer: `HTML stands for Hypertext Markup Language, whereas XHTML stands for Extensible Markup Language.
    A static webpage is an HTML web page and dynamic web pages are XHTML.
    XHTML are more stricter than HTML.
    An XML application of HTML is defined as XHTML.
    All modern browsers support XHTML. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `56. What are Web Workers?`,
    answer: `Web Workers is a code of JavaScript which runs in the background threads without disturbing the performance of the page. It is used for computing-heavy tasks like an access database or function. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `57. What is Quirks mode in HTML5?`,
    answer: `If we do not include the <!DOCTYPE> element in our HTML page or Document, it will go to Quirks Mode. In this mode, the HTML element depends on the browser. Hence the content will be displayed according to the browser. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `58. How Do I Make A Form So It Can Be Submitted By Hitting Enter?

    `,
    answer: `the form should just have one <INPUT TYPE=TEXT> and no TEXTAREA, though it can have other form elements like checkboxes and radio buttons. `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `59. HTML data-* Attribute`,
    answer: `The data-* attribute is used to store custom data private to the page or application.

    The data-* attribute gives us the ability to embed custom data attributes on all HTML elements.
    
    The stored (custom) data can then be used in the page's JavaScript to create a more engaging user experience (without any Ajax calls or server-side database queries).
    
    The data-* attribute consist of two parts:
    
    The attribute name should not contain any uppercase letters, and must be at least one character long after the prefix "data-"
    The attribute value can be any string **** <ul>
    <li data-animal-type="bird">Owl</li>
    <li data-animal-type="fish">Salmon</li>
    <li data-animal-type="spider">Tarantula</li>
  </ul>******`,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `60. `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `61. `,
    answer: ` `,
  },
  {
    id: "h1",
    language: "Html",
    question: `62. `,
    answer: ` `,
  },



];
